a lot of people don't like math and I
think you know when it happens it's when
you're in school and all of a sudden is
stopped being applicable to regular life
isn't that kind of like remember adding
and subtracting nobody hated that
because it's useful in regular life with
regular everyday problems you know like
say there's 13 of us right we have a
12-pack of beer you got to figure it out
right 12 of you need to leave
and thanks so much for talking to me I
appreciate out about the college and uh
because I was gonna show you guys all
clapped when I said about colleges you
go this is a smart crowd like I'm not
I'm not just saying that I can tell
immediately you guys are gonna be a good
crowd and a smoker there's that's not
sure every night for us okay every night
is not like I was doing a show last week
I was in whatever city makes it funny
for you and so I come on go anybody here
you know go to college you know make
some noise where you guys had clapped
that place dead silence seriously nobody
clapped people were just looking to me
like angry that I had brought it up
so his panic and I'm like I gotta change
this question you know so some people
going to answer so I go that's okay you
know and anybody here ever know anybody
that went to college nobody
anybody ever drive by a college anybody
know how to spell college
what if I let you work in groups
has anyone ever made a collage
[Music]
thank you so much for laughing at that
they did not laugh at it
and whatever city you picked
this one guy came up after the show and
he was like I hate comedy guy and I was
like what's up man you know and he go he
goes what in the heck's the studio
apartment and so I explained in what it
was he'd never heard of it you know and
he goes do you realize for that much
money that you spent you could get in
this town like a 10 bedroom house on
about 20 acres of land and I was like I
know man but the only problem is out the
front door you got yeah I live here
some people got offended by that we
didn't even name the place there's like
all those poor people of that fake town
they're bad for those four ten people so
been trying to get in shape it starts to
start getting in shape you guys look
good here
by the way you guys look you guys look
really good too have any big workout
fanatics here tonight with us big
workout fans anybody ever know anybody
the work
[Applause]
anybody who worked outside a gardener
anybody
I have a worked out on a collage hey did
you know Drybar comedy has their very
own app you can check it out men
download it right now it'll take two
seconds you can watch save and share
clips and you can watch my entire
special right there on the app